I think it's a big ship
it's the most comfortable organization I've been in
this organization brings together a group of like-minded people
this group of people
has different backgrounds
skills or ideas
but they have a common characteristic
that is, they have a conscience (LX in Chinese)
interested in Web3
want to explore more possibilities of Web3
reliable, conscientious, practical, and not hyped
some people who are more long-term or idealistic
and on the one hand
they are filled with the pragmatic spirit of engineers
at the same time, they are not lacking in romanticism
and the sentiment of optimism
it is like a pure land of Web3
actually
in here, what we discuss is not so much about
how to speculate on coins
how to make speculative investments
but more focus is on LXDAO
as a DAO, it can do this for
what can it do for the Web3 ecosystem
LXDAO is still actively exploring Web3
public goods
some sustainable solutions
what everyone talks about every day
actually, it's all about some technology
and some things that are oriented
yes
less speculative
or from a financial perspective
mostly about some projects and some
or doing things from the perspective of some products
I think LXDAO is an open
free and equal organization
and LXDAO is made up of a group
of people who basically haven't met much
formed a community together
and cooperated in a very orderly manner
and incubated so many projects
how much contribution we made
how much value we produced
everything is closely related to our own efforts
the more you contribute, the more valuable your contribution is
the more you speak in this DAO organization, the more authority you have
I think LXDAO is a very loving organization
the partners here are very passionate
but they are passionate and have a conscience
you can find some
very passionate people here
and they are happy to
give you some advice or answer your questions
they are willing to answer
for example, Bruce
he was very enthusiastic to help me when I had questions
after finishing the chat
I realized it was midnight for him
I was quite touched by this
as a pure newbie joining LXDAO
to be honest, there were many things I didn't understand at the beginning
for something
I even hesitated to ask buddies
but once I plucked up the courage
I contacted Ache privately
but Ache seemed to sense my anxiety
he replied saying
the mission of LXDAO is to
welcome 10 billion users to Web3
we are also actively doing some things
and helping newcomers enter the world of Web3
for example, our "My First NFT" and "My First Layer2".
help newcomers quickly understand Web3
and safely enter this world
therefore, I believe LXDAO
it is a
very good entry point
with the right attitude to enter Web3
that can help more people
enter the world of Web3
hello, I am WangTeng
a UI designer
I got to know LXDAO through the GCLX (LXDAO's first NFT project)
at that time, I found it very interesting
and wanted to know the people behind it
it was Bruce and Muxin at first
and then I had the opportunity to join LXDAO
And the second question is
Why choose to participate in LXDAO
I feel that LXDAO is very professional
In the field of Web3
And it's also a group of very professional people inside
Doing things
Another reason is
LXDAO actually has another name called "Appearance DAO"
There are really many attractive and good-looking men and women in our LXDAO
Yes, right
We hope that everyone
Can come and take a look
Hello everyone, I am Muxin.
One of the co-initiators of LXDAO.
Initially, I collaborated with Bruce on
the project "GCLX NFT".
Then later, we initiated "My First NFT"
in the community.
At that time, everyone gathered because of "GCLX NFT".
and came together.
When Bruce proposed this idea,
many people responded.
and actively participated in its construction.
Actually, everyone didn't know each other.
and just because of an idea,
they identified with this idea,
wanted to contribute their part,
and gathered together.
and successfully completed the project.
So, I found it very interesting.
and this experience,
I never had it before in my past.
And then, we were also thinking
if we could establish a DAO organization
and gather more people with the same thoughts
to do more valuable things
So, LXDAO was established
Hello everyone
Hello everyone, I am Sanzhi
Currently, I am in the operations team of LXDAO
Then, I collaborated with Bruce
around February or March last year
I got to know Bruce through "My First NFT"
He had a recruitment post at that time
After adding Bruce on WeChat
I joined LXDAO
around December
Because I saw he was recruiting for operations
I went to the weekly meeting
and introduced myself
My self-introduction was quite
honest. I said, "Hello, I am Sanzhi."
And I don't have
much experience in operations
But I've been doing planning
especially event planning
I'm quite skilled in this area.
If you all don't mind
and are willing to give me a chance
I'd be happy to join LXDAO
as a member
and then I started my journey inside LXDAO
And the second question,
why I chose to participate in LXDAO,
Firstly,
I actually see the potential in the entire Web3 ecosystem.
And as for LXDAO,
a friend mentioned it to me before,
he felt that LXDAO has the capability
from an idea to a product,
there's potential,
it's like a dream factory here.
It can turn your ideas
into realized products.
I have ideas too,
so,
I want
my ideas to blossom here.
Hi everyone, I am Cikey,
today let's talk about LXDAO.
My first encounter with LXDAO was,
Actually, it was because of Sanzhi,
At that time, we were both volunteering in Haimen,
She was always so passionate,
immersing herself in her endeavors,
which made me very curious,
her unwavering focus,
as if the noise around her
couldn't touch her,
because we all loved to have fun back then,
but she was always
unaffected,
I started to wonder,
what exactly was it
that ignited her passion so much,
that she'd dive into it without hesitation,
LXDAO, as the first DAO I came across,
started my novice exploration journey in Web3,
So, why did I join LXDAO?
Actually, the answer is simple,
I feel it's not just an organization,
but a vibrant community full of opportunities,
I'm attracted by this interest-driven
and passion-driven collaboration,
I hope to continuously
learn and grow in this creative
and open environment,
to evolve,
and explore with like-minded friends,
the unknown future of Web3,
Also, another point is,
Hey, look at the sea behind me.
Is this also a reason why I joined?
Because it feels like it's not bound
by time and space,
possessing endless possibilities.
Hello everyone,
I am Bruce, one of co-initiators of LXDAO.
Actually, last year,
I initially
launched a project called "My First NFT".
And this project,
is a completely free, charitable NFT
tutorial,
including how to buy and sell NFTs and
how to perform safe operations.
Then, when I made this proposal,
it attracted over 20 friends
to co-build this project together.
This was quite astonishing to me,
because it made me realize
in this speculative
or impetuous Web3 world,
there's still a group of people
willing to invest time in things
that can promote Web3
development.
And this group of people,
I believe they need a place
where everyone can communicate, learn,
and even collaborate on projects.
And LXDAO is such a place.
I am one of those people.
At first,
I got to know about the EIP Fun project.
Then, I joined the EIP Fun Telegram group,
and I've been lurking there.
While lurking,
I got to know about LXDAO.
After getting to know it, I followed its Official Account.
Gradually, with deeper discussions and learning,
I realized that
the purpose of LXDAO is to sustainably support
the development of public goods.
With a deeper understanding of public goods,
I realized that
it's a very meaningful thing.
Why do I say that?
In real life, public goods are like water,
air, sunlight,
roads, lighting systems,
and parks.
And we know that
these things often determine
the development of a region or country.
Their development,
has a significant impact
on their economic model.
So, in certain areas, it's a fundamental factor.
So, when it comes to the internet realm,
internet public products,
undoubtedly,
are the cornerstone of the entire internet ecosystem.
What we are doing now,
supporting Web3 public goods,
this vision, this goal,
is to create a better
ecosystem for Web3,
more positive,
sustainable, and upward-moving ecosystem.
So, with deeper discussions and deeper learning,
then,
In my heart,
The vision of LXDAO
gradually aligns with my personal vision.
I think about building,
constructing such a positive
and active ecosystem.
Such a goal sounds exciting enough.
I believe with such a goal,
it's enough to attract like-minded individuals
to join.
Hello, thanks for the invitation from LXDAO.
First, let's talk about the first question,
how I got to know LXDAO.
Regarding LXDAO,
actually, I first heard about it
at the end of 2021,
when they launched a project called "GCLX NFT"
It became quite popular instantly.
As someone who trades NFTs,
I noticed this project at that time.
But,
unfortunately, I didn't get a chance to buy it.
To buy into this project.
Then, almost a year later,
around November or December of 2022,
I was working on a hackathon project.
This hackathon project
was closely related to Marry3.
So, I did some research on Marry3,
and found out...
behind Marry3 there's an organization called LXDAO.
This organization even writes weekly reports.
My goodness, they're so diligent!
I've never seen a more open and transparent
and truly active
DAO organization.
Because I've been part of some DAO organizations before,
and in reality,
their governance level
doesn't match up to LXDAO's standard.
It made me feel that LXDAO truly understands DAO,
and has a strong DAO consciousness,
and the determination to run a DAO.
So,
I gradually
got involved in some of LXDAO's work.
At first,
I participated in
creating our website page,
and then I joined the development of Donate3
and the My First Layer2 project.
Yes, this is the T-shirt from My First Layer2.
And then,
gradually, I became one of LXDAO's
how should I put it...
Um,
one of the prominent LXP (Core Contributor)
builders.
And actually,
this already answers the second question.
Because...
I truly realized that LXDAO is actively working.
And the direction LXDAO is taking
is really interesting.
It greatly piques my interest.
We are working on public goods.
It's a research and development DAO, right?
What are public goods?
It's actually very
Altruistic outcomes.
For me personally,
How should I put it...
I really derive joy from the process of helping others.
It's fulfilling.
I also hope, as a programmer, to create some
Things that can provide value to others.
Products that truly offer value.
Of course,
The commercial interests
Are actually secondary.
Yes, so,
I think LXDAO can be a place where
I can truly realize my greater potential.
Hello everyone, I am Marcus.
I am currently a game developer.
I am in charge of an AIGC product.
And I also do some
Governance and operational work at LXDAO.
So, how did I get to know LXDAO?
Initially, it was because I joined "GCLX NFT".
This community,
And then became a committed HOLDER of it.
Through this,
I gradually started working with everyone.
And I found that the conversations and chats were very interesting.
The people here are really fascinating.
That kind of feeling.
And then I joined LXDAO.
Later on, "GCLX NFT" also became LXDAO.
Hmm, it was established with a certain gene or foundation.
Actually, I originally had a somewhat negative impression of Chinese Web3 products.
Prejudiced, indeed.
Because I entered the circle relatively early,
And was "rug pulled" by many Chinese Web3 projects.
Yes, that's right.
So, I had some biases against Chinese Web3 products.
But when I bought into this "GCLX NFT" project,
I found it particularly interesting.
Firstly, the design of its website,
And its text, content, and such.
I found it particularly interesting.
It has that ironic feel, performance art.
And after I joined the community,
I realized that everyone was just chatting every day,
Asking the project team for refunds, (joking)
And when the project team would run away.
Such amusing matters.
I was drawn to this community atmosphere.
All because of "GCLX NFT".
This community vibe.
I feel that being with a group of interesting,
and down-to-earth people,
is particularly meaningful.
Hello everyone,
I am Mike.
And the first question is,
How did you get to know LXDAO?
Well, it was over a year ago,
there was an NFT project called "GCLX NFT".
At that time, I approached it with a "do your own research" attitude.
I carefully reviewed the content of the website,
and found it very funny.
But before I could finish,
the NFTs were already minted.
During this process,
I kept a close eye on the development of LXDAO.
At the beginning of this year,
LXDAO launched a project,
called EIP Fun.
I felt that I could learn a lot from it.
I also found it meaningful,
so I signed up for this project.
In the role of a product manager,
I later got to know Bruce,
SanZhi, and other core
builders of LXDAO.
Ah,
The second question is, why did I choose to participate in LXDAO?
I think the core reason is the people,
a group of contributors.
They are very supportive, open, and inclusive,
and also very genuine.
Some people might think that the people in LXDAO
are very amateur,
but in reality, they might be even more professional than you think,
and very native.
Hello everyone, I am Ray.
I first came into contact with LXDAO
through the NFT "GCLX NFT"
At the peak of the NFT market,
which was full of chaos,
"GCLX NFT" emerged,
and I was greatly shocked.
I realized that NFTs could be done this way,
so I minted two on the official website.
They are still in my wallet now,
I don't know if they have become worthless,
I should check later.
After "GCLX NFT"
LXDAO was established.
One thing LXDAO does is
to popularize knowledge about NFTs to everyone,
as well as how to use and mint NFTs.
In this project,
I also contributed some minor modifications.
And during this process, I found out
that the people in LXDAO are indeed
both interesting and conscientious.
So, I applied
to become a builder in LXDAO,
and have been
until today.
Over the past year or so,
I have also witnessed the development of LXDAO.
Hello everyone, I am Samo.
A cross-disciplinary learner who knows a bit about technology,
finance, and macroeconomics.
I had heard about LXDAO before,
but didn't know much about it.
My first impression was that it's an organization focused on public goods.
A public welfare DAO organization.
I'm very interested in popularizing knowledge.
Initially, I was skeptical about the efficiency
of a DAO doing public goods.
But after joining,
I found out that LXDAO has already completed more than ten projects.
I was quite amazed.
At first, I was invited
by a friend to join a popularization project,
which is "My First Layer2".
During the project,
I felt that the atmosphere of this DAO organization was very good.
Firstly, collaborating with the project's designers
and developers was very pleasant.
Also, sometimes during meetings,
and regular communications, I felt everyone was very nice.
I really like the atmosphere here.
Hello everyone, I am Seven.
I first learned about LXDAO
from an article by Bruce.
At that time, what left a deep impression on me was Bruce's understanding
of the two different organizational forms:
DAO and companies.
He made a very vivid analogy,
saying that DAOs and companies
might be like hammers and axes.
When you're nailing,
a hammer is definitely more useful.
But when splitting wood,
an axe is definitely more efficient.
I strongly agree with this perspective.
And I also feel that
LXDAO might be a more
pragmatic,
down-to-earth kind of DAO.
Rather than one that
primarily outputs ideology.
This was my initial impression
of LXDAO.
Then, why did I join LXDAO?
Actually, I joined many Chinese DAO communities at that time,
and I was also observing them,
including their governance rules, style of action,
and the projects they were involved in, etc.
LXDAO gave me a feeling that it was
very sincere and genuine,
down-to-earth without any fluff.
And whether it's their website or products,
be it user experience, design, aesthetics, or professionalism, everything is
on point.
The first product I tried
was "My First NFT".
Wow, I really think that product deserves 99 points.
Haha, yes.
It directly hit the target of the product.
The remaining one point
might be my hope
that they continue to develop it,
enriching the content and expanding it further.
Another thing is that
Because I am an INFP,
I am a very idealistic person.
So,
the word "conscience" (LX) really touches me.
I can feel a very simple and
sincere longing for something better.
Of course, I think it's not just about slogans,
from why the DAO was established,
to all the projects they've done over the year,
including their mission and vision,
governance rules, and the overall community atmosphere,
in every word and deed,
I feel they are very consistent in thought and action.
Yes, this is
what I
truly feel, this sincerity and conscience.
So, I wanted to join.
Even though I'm not a programmer,
and don't have an internet background,
I believe
I hope to contribute
as much as I can here.
Contribute, right.
Of course, I can also learn a lot and make many
conscientious friends here.
Hi everyone,
You can call me Tiao.
I first got to know LXDAO in
around April this year.
At that time, I
I was in the LXDAO English translation WeChat group.
And then I started trying to find some
tasks to do.
Why did I choose to participate in LXDAO?
Well, one reason is that
here,
I can, through my own efforts, obtain some
income.
Of course, well,
in other places,
everyone can earn some income
through their efforts.
But I feel that here,
the distribution of income is more fair and transparent.
Another point is that
I'm personally interested in the Web3 field.
Well, because
I think the Web3 field hasn't been fully defined yet,
it's not structured.
For example, you can see a lot of speculative things here,
Many speculative things,
but at the same time, there are also many imaginative things,
things that are different.
For example, the concept of DAO.
This is also what initially attracted me to Web3.
Things.
So I think that here,
doing things and learning
are meaningful.
Well, and right now, I also want to do some...
I also want to do a graduate thesis related to governance.
I have a background in social sciences myself,
and I think applying what I've learned from other places
to this field
is actually quite interesting.
One interesting thing I find in LXDAO
I find quite interesting.
For example, I think, I think, I think
Marcus is quite interesting.
Hahaha.
Hmm, yes. Previously,
Bruce mentioned in a meeting, he said, "Hey,
Aren't you in New Zealand?
Haven't you been in Singapore for so long?
Your English is so bad."
Everyone is very straightforward and honest.
I find this aspect quite interesting.
The third point I find interesting is
Right from the beginning,
we insist on using DAO and Web3
to run in a native way,
and also gradually decentralize.
At the same time, we adhere to the principle of not free-riding,
although our treasury is not abundant,
we still try to allocate funds within the budget
to contributors who have made contributions.
So, many people don't have high expectations for us,
including myself last year,
but what I find very interesting is
up to now,
This system can indeed operate,
and it's getting better and better.
I think the decentralized office format of our DAO
is very interesting.
For example, in meetings, you'll find some people on vacation,
some by the seaside, some in the countryside, and so on.
As long as everyone has an internet connection, they can work together.
And the efficiency is very high.
I find this interesting.
This is also what I think,
A very interesting point.
Actually, for me personally,
I haven't met any
member of LXDAO in person.
But actually, this doesn't hinder us from working together
on quite a few things.
And actually, the whole process is very smooth,
and there aren't any significant obstacles.
So I think
this kind of LXDAO is very good.
This kind of community atmosphere,
and everyone striving together for a common vision,
working together,
I think that's what attracts me the most
about a place.
The most interesting part, I think, is
because there's no boss or CEO here,
but it seems like everyone knows
how to work together
and at the same time, everyone is learning.
Learning together,
exploring how to work together more efficiently,
and at the same time,
allowing everyone to be free
to work in this way.
Now, LXDAO has over 100 members,
and everyone comes from different fields
with different professional backgrounds.
There are programmers, designers,
product managers, and operations
And investors, consultants,
a variety of backgrounds,
and everyone gathers together
to contribute their ideas.
If others agree with your idea,
you can initiate a proposal
and create a project group
to turn your idea into reality.
And it feels very interesting and cool.
Secondly, it's also about
Although LXDAO now has over 100 members,
in fact,
some of the older members from before are no longer active,
and there are more and more new members joining.
And LXDAO is still
operating very well.
I think this point is quite interesting.
In fact, at the beginning,
LXDAO was organized with
about 20 or so people.
There weren't many people,
but because it was small,
things got done faster
and more efficiently.
But later on,
when LXDAO grew to around 50 or 60 people,
some governance issues arose.
Some of our old members became inactive,
and to achieve voting,
you had to ask some of the old members to
participate in governance.
But these old members might be busy
and not have the time
to carefully review the proposals.
Later on, to address these issues,
we also proposed some methods at the Season Summit,
such as representative systems and more.
Suddenly, we realized
why the Western world has that kind of
democratic system,
and why China has its
system of people's representatives.
I find this area quite interesting.
Just in my opinion,
in fact, the cultural symbol of conscience is the most intriguing.
Why do I say that?
Because the cultural symbol of conscience
naturally requires
everyone who joins LXDAO to have a conscience.
In other words, you must always act with a clear conscience.
Yes, and this point
is something I find particularly interesting.
And we often ask each other
if you have a conscience
and things like that.
I think it's quite intriguing.
Another interesting aspect is LXTalk.
Hope everyone can come and listen
and also hope everyone can
subscribe, like, share, comment. Thank you.
I think it's a group of very interesting people
creating together,
and continuing to create,
conscientious public goods.
If I were to ask a soul-searching question,
what is the meaning of life?
Well, my answer is that life originally has no meaning,
but there is a way to give it meaning,
and that's through creation,
finding a group of people to create with.
It will make you feel more meaningful.
I prepared some
salt
hoping to freshen things up for everyone
and save my video a bit.
If someone introduces you to DAO, what do you think?
I hope LXDAO gets better and better.
I hope LXDAO makes a contribution to Web3.
Incubate more outstanding
Web3 public goods projects that more people use.
And I hope more ideas can
take root and grow here.
I hope it can
go further and further.
And in the Web3 ecosystem,
find its own position
and improve more and more.
The name is a clear vision
a moral motivation
But LX is also something rather different.
I think we need to stick to our original intention
which is conscience
This is a bottom line that cannot be crossed
We should cultivate more conscience genes
That is, spread our cultural symbol of conscience
To pass it on
Whether it's in the Chinese-speaking world or in the whole world
Yes, conscience is actually a rare quality
Right
I also hope that this precious conscience
live long and prosper
There's a saying that goes very well
The meaning of work
is a group of people with feelings and righteousness doing
meaningful things together
Many companies may say this
But I think LXDAO is doing it
And I hope LXDAO's influence will grow
And it can attract
More and more real builders.
And together make this society better
I feel very honored to be able to
explore Web3 and future collaboration with everyone
in this very early stage
Because during this period
it's likely that it will be gone in a few years
And I also hope that some interested friends
can join us
And we can explore together in this early stage
Do some interesting things
And solve some meaningful problems
Of course, I think in the next stage
There might be a need
To consider more business models
To make us the strongest
Developer community in the Chinese-speaking region
As a builder
And at the same time
Also as an owner of our LXDAO
I sincerely hope
That LXDAO can eventually achieve success
To become the strongest DAO organization
In our country
And then
Step out of Asia and go global
Wishing everyone the best
Together we rise higher
Climate crisis
What will crypto going to deal with Anthropocene
And also, besides that
Let's gather more
Within the team
All the members of LXDAO might consider organizing more events in the future
To come together more
Yes
Although the story
And then, I want to say to Web...
Conscience
I want to say to LXDAO
What should I say
What I want to say to LXDAO is...
and it's you that write the story